what does discipline really mean you
know besides waking up early and how do
I employ it to all aspects of my life
what does it really
mean yes
discipline it it does start with waking
up early it really
does but that is just the
beginning and I always say that
discipline is the root of all good
qualities
but you you have to absolutely apply it
to things outside of just waking up
early it's it's everything it's working
out every day making yourself stronger
and faster and more flexible and
healthier discipline is eating the right
foods to fuel your
system it it's about disciplining your
emotions
so you can make good decisions it's
about having the discipline to control
your
ego so your ego doesn't get out of hand
and control
you it's about treating people the way
you would want to be
treated and and doing the tasks that you
don't necessarily want to do but that
you know will help you or help your team
it's
about facing your
fears takes discipline to face your
fears so you can conquer
them and that's what discipline is
discipline means taking the Hard Road
the uphill road to do what's right for
yourself and for other people
it's so often the easy
path the easy path that calls to us to
be weak for that moment to break down
for that
moment to give in to the desire and the
shortterm
gratification but the discipline will
not allow that the discipline calls for
strength and fortitude and
will it won't accept weakness it won't
tolerate another
breakdown the discipline can
seem like it's your worst
enemy but the reality
is discipline is your best friend it
will take care of you like nothing else
can and it'll will put you on that
path the path to strength and health and
intelligence and
happiness and most
importantly it'll put you on that
path to Freedom